deerwalk.com 2015-06-27

# Deerwalk | Privacy Policy

At Deerwalk, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. The detail below describes the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our site, and the measures we take to safeguard your information.

### Log Files

Similar to most other website owners, Deerwalk collects and uses anonymous information such as the name of your ISP, browser used, connection speed, date and time of visit and the pages you access. This data does not provide the specific identification of any particular user, but is aggregated with all other visitor information. The information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends and provide a better experience for our readers.

### Cookies

This website may use cookies to track information relevant to affiliate marketing and advertising, and to improve the user experience. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. 

### Links

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We suggest that you read the privacy statement of each site you visit that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site. 

### Acceptance of this Policy and Concerns

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this site’s privacy policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time.   
If you feel that we have not followed this website’s stated privacy policy, please contact us.
